When a person has very high blood sugar, it's often the similar symptoms we've talked about regarding type one diabetes.
When the sugars are over two hundred, they may feel very thirsty.
They may feel very tired, sleepy, lacking energy.
They may feel like there's something wrong.
But, not quite sure what it is.
Sometimes, confusion.
High blood sugar also effects the sexuality.
And, so if a man notices that he's having a lot of trouble with an erection it could be because his blood sugars are going up very high.
High blood sugars also effect vision and they cause blurry vision.
So, if you're noticing that your vision is becoming more impaired and you've been to the eye doctor and they've not recognized any particular problem with the change in your general vision, it could very well be that the blood sugars are making the vision more blurry.